http://www.hinesindustries.com/privacy

Click to Call
IndustriesAgriculture & Small EngineAutomotive & Industrial TruckAviation & Aerospace / SpaceConstruction / Heavy Equipment / Industrial TruckDefenseElectric Motor / Electrical IndustryEnergy, Power Generation & PumpsFans & BlowersHousehold Appliances & Power ToolsMarineMedicalRail / Mass TransitResearch & DevelopmentProduct RangeAutomated Balancing MachinesAutomated Manufacturing CellsMulti-Station Balancing MachinesSpecialty MachinesStandard Balancing MachinesHorizontal Cradle Balancing MachinesHorizontal Overhung Spindle Balancing MachinesVertical Spindle Balancing MachinesStatic Balancing MachinesHC5000 For SaleHigh Performance & Aftermarket Balancing MachinesDrive Line BalancersLegend Series Engine BalancersHollow Spindle Tube Lathe (HSTL)Push-Out Press (POP)Push-Up Press (PUP)Shaft Rebuilder (PSWS)Shaft Straightening PressStraightening MachinesMoment Matching MachinesMass Centering MachinesGaugingSpecialty LathesRod Matching & Sorting MachinesRefurbishment & RetrofitUsed Balancing Machines Correction MethodsApplicationsAirplane Propeller Balancing MachinesAnode X-ray Tube Balancing MachinesArmature Balancing MachineArmature Balancing Machine With Single StationArmature Balancing Machine, Fully AutomaticArmature Balancing Machine, LargeArmature Balancing Machine With Two StationsAutonomous Sensor and Lidar Balancing MachinesBalance Shaft Balancing MachineBlade Balancing MachineBlower Wheel Balancing MachinesBrake Balancing Machines, AutomaticClutch Balancing MachineCombine Rotor Balancing MachinesConnecting Rod Weighing, Matching & SortingCoupling Balancing MachineCV Assembly Balancing MachineDamper Balancing MachineDifferential Balancing MachineEngine Balancing MachineEngine Component Balancing MachineFan Balancing MachineFlange Balancing Machines & Yoke Balancing MachinesFlexplate Balancing MachinesFlywheel Balancing MachineFlywheel Magneto Balancing MachineGear Balancing MachineGrinding Wheel Balancing MachinesHub Balancing MachineLasersMotor Fan Balancing MachinePropeller Balancing MachinesPump Impeller Balancing MachineRefinery Plate Balancing MachinesRoboticsSheave/Pulley Balancing MachinesSupercharger Balancing MachinesTransmission Component Balancing MachineToolingToolholder And Tool Balancing MachinesTorque Converter Balancing MachineTurbine Balancing MachineTurbocharger Balancing MachineViscous Coupler Balancing MachineWheel BalancerWood Chipper Balancing MachinesServicesCustomer ServiceRequest ServiceCalibration & CertificationOrder Spare PartsFAQsContact Customer ServiceBalancing ServiceScheduled Maintenance ServiceComputer UpgradesRefurbishmentWindows Package for Industrial MachinesWindows Package for Legend MachinesBalancing Equipment Trade-Ins Product Optimization ServiceTraining & Seminars
IndustriesAgriculture & Small EngineAutomotive & Industrial TruckAviation & Aerospace / SpaceConstruction / Heavy Equipment / Industrial TruckDefenseElectric Motor / Electrical IndustryEnergy, Power Generation & PumpsFans & BlowersHousehold Appliances & Power ToolsMarineMedicalRail / Mass TransitResearch & DevelopmentProduct RangeAutomated Balancing MachinesAutomated Manufacturing CellsMulti-Station Balancing MachinesSpecialty MachinesStandard Balancing MachinesHorizontal Cradle Balancing MachinesHorizontal Overhung Spindle Balancing MachinesVertical Spindle Balancing MachinesStatic Balancing MachinesHC5000 For SaleHigh Performance & Aftermarket Balancing MachinesDrive Line BalancersLegend Series Engine BalancersHollow Spindle Tube Lathe (HSTL)Push-Out Press (POP)Push-Up Press (PUP)Shaft Rebuilder (PSWS)Shaft Straightening PressStraightening MachinesMoment Matching MachinesMass Centering MachinesGaugingSpecialty LathesRod Matching & Sorting MachinesRefurbishment & RetrofitUsed Balancing Machines Correction MethodsApplicationsAirplane Propeller Balancing MachinesAnode X-ray Tube Balancing MachinesArmature Balancing MachineArmature Balancing Machine With Single StationArmature Balancing Machine, Fully AutomaticArmature Balancing Machine, LargeArmature Balancing Machine With Two StationsAutonomous Sensor and Lidar Balancing MachinesBalance Shaft Balancing MachineBlade Balancing MachineBlower Wheel Balancing MachinesBrake Balancing Machines, AutomaticClutch Balancing MachineCombine Rotor Balancing MachinesConnecting Rod Weighing, Matching & SortingCoupling Balancing MachineCV Assembly Balancing MachineDamper Balancing MachineDifferential Balancing MachineEngine Balancing MachineEngine Component Balancing MachineFan Balancing MachineFlange Balancing Machines & Yoke Balancing MachinesFlexplate Balancing MachinesFlywheel Balancing MachineFlywheel Magneto Balancing MachineGear Balancing MachineGrinding Wheel Balancing MachinesHub Balancing MachineLasersMotor Fan Balancing MachinePropeller Balancing MachinesPump Impeller Balancing MachineRefinery Plate Balancing MachinesRoboticsSheave/Pulley Balancing MachinesSupercharger Balancing MachinesTransmission Component Balancing MachineToolingToolholder And Tool Balancing MachinesTorque Converter Balancing MachineTurbine Balancing MachineTurbocharger Balancing MachineViscous Coupler Balancing MachineWheel BalancerWood Chipper Balancing MachinesServicesCustomer ServiceRequest ServiceCalibration & CertificationOrder Spare PartsFAQsContact Customer ServiceBalancing ServiceScheduled Maintenance ServiceComputer UpgradesRefurbishmentWindows Package for Industrial MachinesWindows Package for Legend MachinesBalancing Equipment Trade-Ins Product Optimization ServiceTraining & Seminars
About HinesDesign ExcellenceHistoryHines CustomersNews & EventsCorporate Social ResponsibilityCareersResourcesArticlesVideosBalancing TipsFAQConversion Chart ISO Tolerance Calculator Contact usRequest a Machine QuoteRequest ServiceOrder Spare PartsRequest More Information
Contact Hines
Hines Industries, Inc. 240 Metty Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 48103-9498 USA +1 (734) 769-2300
HomePrivacy
Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.
The following outlines our privacy policy:
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Contact Hines
Latest News
November 30, 2020
Hines Manufactures First Autonomous Sensor Balancing Machine
See All News From Hines
Not Finding what you're looking for? Let us help. Click here or Call (734) 769-2300.
